// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Which class acts as a root for all java classes?",
    answer: "Object",
    options: [
      "String",
      "Object",
      "Throwable",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Using the concept of encapsulation security of the data is ---------------",
    answer: "Ensured to some extent",
    options: [
      "Ensured to some extent",
      "Purely ensured",
      "Not ensure",
      "very low"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "______is implemented as Combination of methods and attributes into a class",
    answer: "Encapsulation",
    options: [
      "Encapsulation",
      "Inheritance",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
      ]
      
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not a kind of exception that is thrown by the JDBC method?",
    answer: "Data Rounding",
    options: [
      "Data Rounding",
      "SQL Exception",
      "SQL Rounding",
      "Data Truncation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many objects can be referenced from the same variables?",
    answer: "One at a time",
    options: [
      "One at a time",
      "Many at a time",
      "Many using array name",
      "7 at max at same time"
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "What is the range of boolean data type in java",
     answer: "Not Applicable",
     options: [
       "-128 to 127",
       "0 to 65535",
       "-32768 to 32767",
       "Not Applicable"
     ]
   },
    {
     numb: 7,
     question: "Which data type is best suited to represent the logical values?",
     answer: "Boolean",
     options: [
       "Boolean",
       "String",
       "Integer",
       "Float"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "Two methods with the same name but different argument types are known as?",
     answer: "Method overloading",
     options: [
       "Method overloading",
       "Method overriding",
       "Constructor overriding",
       "Both A and B"
     ]
   },
  {
     numb: 9,
     question: "The subclass constructor uses the ———keyword to invoke the constructor of the superclass",
     answer: "Super",
     options: [
       "Super",
       "Final",
       "Static",
       "Public"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Which of the following is a correct way to create an object of class Test? ",
     answer: "Test t=new Test();",
     options: [
       "Test t=new Test();",
       "Test t=new Test;",
       "t=new Test();",
       "new Test t;"
     ]
   },
  

  







];